### **Demetria Perry**

Milwaukee, WI | 414-366-9743 demetria\_p@yahoo.com

### **Summary**

I like to work hard and have fun. I am a detail-oriented, analytical, and self-driven programmer with extensive experience building user-facing applications. Efficient and knowledgeable coder with skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript programming languages. I am a self-motivated, adaptable, and reliable front end web developer that would be a great asset to your team.

#### **Portfolio**

My Portfolio

https://deeperry.github.io/perry.github.io/

### Experience

# Freelance/Self Employed | Wisconsin, Milwaukee Web Developer | 04/2022 - Present

- Meet with clients to discuss their website design and requirements
- Create and test apps for the website
- Code for the site using HTML,CSS, and JavaScript
- Engage with members of their team to ascertain the kind of information the site should contain
- Design wireframes with Figma or XD
- Quality-test and troubleshoot the website in various browsers and device views

### Converge Technology Solutions | WI, Milwaukee Help Desk Analyst | 10/2020 - Present

- Provide help desk support to over 15 different companies
- Ticket systems cherwell, service-now, freshservice
- Install and configure hardware and software components
- Provide detailed descriptions of the issue in a note format
- Troubleshoot VPN Global protect, vmware, Citrix
- Reference the knowledge base and other resources to resolve issue independently
- Troubleshoot hardware and software issues
- Communicate technical information in a non-technical fashion to provide support

# Brady Corporation | WI, Milwaukee IT Engineer | 06/2016 - 09/2020

- Troubleshoot hardware and software issues via remote or in person
- Set up new user accounts, profiles, and password issues within Active Directory
- Respond to tickets and emails in a reasonable amount of time in ServiceNow
- Report and troubleshoot network issues
- Work on a team or independently

### Skills

Customer service, Html5, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, React, Node.JS, SQL, AWS, Adobe Creative Suite, figma

#### Education

ITT Technical Institute | Greenfield, Wisconsin Information Systems and Security | 04/2013

ITT Technical Institute | Greenfield, Wisconsin Computer Networking | 06/2009 Perfect attendance